SSMAP FIX ======
Start the game, 
when u are at the startscreen (NOT IN THE GAME!) Go to grafics,
 and have ur screen at fullscreen as standart if u dont have that change it and restart game... 
Then change it to off and Apply,
 then to borderless and Apply,
 and then back to fullscreen and apply.
 Then resume ur game. 
When u get into the game, the Map Will work.
 U Will need to do this everytime u start the game, but it seems to work everytime for me and some others :)﻿